

Joseph Sarfo Boadi → Helsinki-Finland → +358449897411 Fullstack Web Developer sarfojoee@gmail.com

sarfojoe co sarfojoe () joseph-sarfo-boadi-377735197

A dedicated and passionate Full Stack Web Developer with experience focusing predominantly on Javascript (React.Js and Node.Js) but always able to adapt to new learning environments. With my background as an Educationist, a Science Teacher, a Sale Manager, and the full stack learning experience at the Helsinki Business College has given me the advantage to excel in collaborating or working individually as demonstrated in each project and throughout my career.

Skills: React.js Node.js CSS Redux Data Structures HTML JavaScript UI-Design and Prototype Redux

Firebase Mongo, Mongoose Express

Experience

Swiss Medica 21 century

Oct 2015 to Jul 2016

Sales manager Moscow-Russia

Worked closely with medical practitioners to maintain optimum levels of communication for the effective and efficient completion of treatment for patients seeking stem cell medication.

West African Examination Council (WAEC)

Oct 2011 to Aug 2015

Examiner Kumasi-Ghana

Examiner of Integrated Science for the final external examination of Senior High Schools (WASSCE) in Ghana organized by the West African Examination Council (WAEC)

Ghana Education Service (Opoku Ware High School)

Sep 2011 to Aug 2015

Science Teacher Kumasi-Ghana

- -Taught academic scientific concepts, clearly explaining modern uses and implications to make the curriculum relevant to everyday life.
- -Built productive, professional student-teacher relationships through a dialogic teaching approach, providing a safe, positive learning environment.

Education

Helsinki Business College

Jan 2020 to Dec 2020

Fullstack Web Developer

University of Jyväskylä, Finland

Sep 2016 to Apr 2019

Master of Arts, Educational Leadership

University of Education, Winneba-Ghana

Sep 2007 to Jun 2011

Bachelor of Education, Integrated Science

Wesley College of Education, Kumasi-Ghana

Sep 2002 to Jun 2005

Teacher's Certificate 'A', Education

Projects

covid-19-tracker

An application made with React.Js, axios, API, and CSS, to track the update of Covid-19 cases all over the world

JavaScript, CSS, HTML

movie-library

movie-library-7598c.web.app/ github.com/sarfojoe/movie-library

A Netflix clone made with React.Js, material-UI, API, axios. This app enables you to watch movie trailers

CSS, JavaScript, HTML

traveldiaries

traveldiaries-fd7aa.web.app/ github.com/sarfojoe/traveldiaries

A group work of fullstack (Node.Js and React.Js) app for people who travel all over the world. This app enables you to mark all places visited in the world, share pictures and add comments for people who want to visit there

JavaScript, HTML, CSS

react-redux-social-network-app

A full stack app for social networking where people are able to register and log in to create and share a post.

HTML, JavaScript, CSS